http://www.welectronics.com/privacy-policy

NEW! Check Out the Latest in 5G Technology !!! Click Here!
Send E-mail
Answer within 24 Hours (excluding weekends).
Privacy Policy
We take your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy lets you know what
information we collect, share, and your choices regarding sharing of your
information. This policy applies to Overseas Electronics Inc.,
dba-Welectronics.com and other places where we may collect personal information.
If you have any questions or concerns you may email us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
(subject: Privacy) further you may mail us at:
Overseas Electronics Inc. dba/ Welectronics.com
2457 W. Devon Ave
Chicago, IL 60659-1914
Information We Collect
• Any information you give us, such as during transactions, customer service,
surveys, social media, and online registrations.
• Any information from other sources, such as consumer reporting agencies, and
• Any information automatically collected when you visit our websites, such as
via cookies, metadata on website, and in stores, e.g. via video cameras.
How we use
that information
Overseas Electronics Inc. does not sell or rent any of your private
information to third parties. We may share or disclose your personal data
for the purposes set out in below to third parties. The Third Parties
Include:
Service
Providers
Such
service providers may include:
merchant banks for authorization and approval, in order to process your credit
card information to complete your orders/transactions. This process is protected
by an enhanced security system. See section 9 below for more details on security
measures and procedures; third-party companies to perform functions on our
behalf e.g. order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal
and email delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing; and
IT
cloud and hosting providers.
Advisors
Such
advisors may include legal, financial, business or other advisors.
Affiliated
website platform and social media users
As
mentioned above, any personal data you make available publicly such as by your
reviews, comments or testimonials will be shared with other users of the Site.
Affiliated
companies
We may
share your personal data we collect with all Overseas Electronics, Inc.
subsidiaries and affiliates.
As our
business continues to evolve, we may acquire, establish or sell business units
or subsidiaries. Customer data is one of the business assets that would be
transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personal
data would only be used in a manner consistent with this privacy policy.
Third
parties as required by law or regulation
We may
disclose your personal data as required by law or regulation, and when we
believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a
judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Overseas
Electronics, Inc.
Third-party companies for marketing
Subject to your marketing preferences and settings, we may share your personal
data with third-party companies that may, among other things, use your personal
data to provide you with targeted advertisements and special offers. You can
change your settings via Account Settings, or by contacting us.
Overseas Electronics Inc. uses the information to improve functions such as
customer service, logistics, and internal operations etc.
Overseas Electronics Inc. may share certain personal information with third
parties such as financial institutions, credit card companies, and if a need
arises to protect and support Overseas Electronics Inc. and its affiliates.
To
conduct our business and provide you with our services and access to our
Site
To
manage your account and subscriptions
To
communicate with you (about updates and changes) and provide you with
customer support
To
facilitate payments
In
relation to fraud prevention
To
allow you to use interactive features of the Site
To
ensure our Site content is relevant and to maintain the security of our Site
For
research and development purposes
To
administer contests/sweepstakes
To
provide you with marketing materials
To use
with Mobile applications and website analytics
To
enforce our terms and in connection with legal or regulatory obligations
To
reorganize or make changes to our business
Consumer
Opt Out
Overseas Electronics Inc. does communicate and market certain products via
email or mail, but the option is left to the consumer if they would like to
receive such promotions.
Overseas Electronics Inc. uses an opt-out standard for such communications
and will not further communicate if the consumer opts-out of such
communication.
Legal
Necessities
We may
share your information in other special circumstances. These include situations
when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or that the sharing is
necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Overseas
Electronics Inc., our customers, our associates, or any other person. Examples
include protecting the health or safety of customers, or addressing crimes
committed on Overseas Electronics Inc. property. Data from in-store security
cameras may also be provided to law enforcement upon written request.
Consumer Opt Out
• Overseas Electronics Inc. does communicate and market certain products via
email or mail, but the option is left to the consumer if they would like to
receive such promotions.
• Overseas Electronics Inc. uses an opt-out standard for such communications and
will not further communicate if the consumer opts-out of such communication.
Security
No data transmission over the Internet or websites can be guaranteed to be
secure from intrusion. However, Overseas Electronics, Inc. takes commercially
reasonable efforts to protect its customers’ personal data. We use industry
standard security 128 bit encrypted SSL servers. Welectronics.com. takes
precautions to protect its customers' information.
When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information
(such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is
protected with the best encryption software currently available in the industry
- SSL. Welectronics.com uses the most advanced form of SSL software available:
128-bit encryption by Cart32™. To learn more about SSL, follow this link
www.cart32.com. Welectronics.com is
certified by McAfee™ Security. The McAfee SECURE™ Trustmark only appears when
the website has passed McAfee’s intensive, daily security scan. McAfee test for
possible personal information access, links to dangerous sites, phishing, and
other online dangers.
Welectronics.com accepts Google™ Checkout for payments on purchases. To
access Google Checkout’s privacy policy please go to:
https://checkout.google.com/files/privacy.html  Welectronics.com
accepts Paypal™ for payments on purchases. To access Paypal’s Privacy Policy
please go to:
https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US
Overseas Electronics Chicago and its Employees will never ask for a money
gram or western union money transfer . We are not listed on Alibaba or sell on
Aliexpress . Give us a call or email us as we are available during our Business
hours for any questions or Concerns.
Questions
Please email us if you have any questions at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. (Subject: Privacy),
or you may Mail in your request at:
Overseas Electronics Inc. dba/ Welectronics.com
2457 W. Devon Ave
Chicago, IL 60659-1914
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
Information
FAQContact usShipping and PaymentProduct InfoOrder Status
Policies
Term of UsePrivacy PolicyReturn PolicySpecial Order itemsWarranty
Contact us
Address: 2457 W. Devon Ave. Chicago, IL 60659, USA
Email: labbek@aol.com
Phone: 1.773.274.3764
© 1997-2020 OVERSEAS ELECTRONICS Chicago IL . All Rights Reserved. OVERSEAS Electronics is not affiliated with any product manufacturer. Products carry manufacturer's warranty only. Logos, trademarks, names, images, etc. are property of their respective companies.
